Guide to the Stuart Saunders Smith papers ARCH174
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
- Compositions, 1967-2018; I
  - Compositions by Others, 1979-2018; undated
    - For The Graduation, 2011 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 18)
      Written by Carson Cooman for a capella choir.
    - Christian Music, circa 2012 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 19)
      Written by Larry Polansky for indeterminate ensemble.
    - The Evening Choir, 2012 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 20)
      Written by Carson Cooman for SATB choir, SATB soloists, and organ.
    - Morning at Brant Point, 2012 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 21)
      Written by Carson Cooman for viola and cello.
    - Simantron, 2012 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 22)
      Written by Sylvie Lacroix for flute, oboe, Bb clarinet, piano, and strings.
    - Three Songs for Tom and Joe, 2012 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 23)
      Written by Larry Polansky for voice and piano.
    - Centenary Fragment (Stravinsky-Cage), 2013 (Box Compositions 14, Folder 24)
      Written by Christopher Shultis for flute, Bb clarinet, vibraphone, violin, and cello.
    - Is Ubiquity the Opposite of Art, undated (Box Compositions 14, Folder 25)
      Written by Robert McCormick for solo snare drum.
    - The Motive for Metaphor, undated (Box Compositions 14, Folder 26)
      Written by Michael Berkowitz for flute, Bb clarinet, and cello.
    - Notebook (Bass clef version), undated (Box Compositions 14, Folder 27)
      Written by Hoffman for solo bass clef instrument.
    - The Sound of a Few Leaves, undated (Box Compositions 14, Folder 28)
      Written by Michael Berkowitz for Bb clarinet and cello.
- Recordings, 1970-2018; II
  Within this series is a varied collection of recordings of Stuart Saunders Smith's compositions. Several of the recordings are released albums that feature Smith's works, as well as albums on which a work of his was included. Several of the artists on the album are world-renowned ensembles and musicians such as: So Percussion, McCormick Percussion Ensemble, Bert Turetzky, Kyle Adam Blair, and Berndt Thurner. While there are many published albums in the collection, a great deal of the pieces are live recordings of concerts of Smith's works, recorded rehearsals, and some rough mixes of studio recordings. The vast majority of the recordings in the collection are CD's, though there are various audiocassettes, LP's, and quarter-inch audio reels, in addition to several video formats (DVD and VHS). There are also several recordings of works by Smith's friends and colleagues (which oftentimes were acquired via correspondence).
  The Recordings series is arranged into two sub-series: a. Recordings of Smith and his works and b. Recordings of others.
  - Recordings of Smith and his works, 1970-2018
    This sub-series contains recordings that feature at least one performance and/or composition by Stuart Saunders Smith. Included within the sub-series are professionally mixed and released albums, recorded concerts, rehearsals, as well as run-throughs of works and in-progress mixes of compositions to be released on albums.
    The recordings are arranged chronologically.
    - Stuart Saunders Smith 1970 Senior Recital, 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Percussion in Chamber Music, 1972 (Box Correspondence 6, Folder 2)
      This file consists of only drafts of linear notes for a recording "Percussion in Chamber Music," by The World (Inc.) Music Ensemble, a group of Hartford Area Composers and performers which, among others, included Stuart Saunders Smith, David Macbride, and Ed Diemente. The recording itself is not part of the collection.
    - Pinetop, 1980 Jul 2; 1 Reels Master 1/4 inch reel 7 inches (Box Shared Audio Reels 1)
      Master recording of Pinetop, performed by Paul Hoffmann (pianist).
    - Music by Stuart Smith, 1981 Sep 16; 1 Reels Master 1/4 inch 7 inches (Box Shared Audio Reels 1)
      Master recording of Music By Stuart Smith, includes Songs I-IX, Poems I, II, and III, and Tit for Tat.
      Performed by Stuart Smith (vocals), Arthur Steinhorn (brake drums), Stuart Smith (narrator).
    - Words in Passing, circa 1986; 1 Cassettes Audiocassette (Box Shared Cassette Box 1)
    - By Language Embellished, 1987 Feb 10; 1 Cassettes Master Betacam L-250 (Box Shared Videotape 1)
      By Language Embellished by Stuart Saunders Smith. 16-bit Resolution Betacam Master.
    - Stuart Smith Reserve Masters, 1987 Jul 24; 1 Reels Master 1/4 inch 7-inch (Box Shared Audio Reels 1)
      Master recording of Tocatta for Violin and Piano.
    - Crux; Stuart Saunders Smith, 1992; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - "And Points North..." Deborah Moore Senior Recital, 1994 Feb 19; 1 Cassettes VHS T-120 (Box Shared Videotape 1)
      "And Points North…" by Stuart Saunders Smith. Performed by Deborah Moore for Senior Recital at Oberlin University.
    - Songs I-IX, performed by Matt Fox, 1994 Apr 15-28; 1 Cassettes VHS T-120 (Box Shared Videotape 1)
      Songs I-IX by Stuart Saunders Smith. Performed by Matt Fox at Kent State Stark Campus on April 15, 1994 and Ashland University April 28th, 1994. Cassette removed from correspondance to Stuart Saunders Smith from Mark Maynor dated May 20, 1994.
    - Two Lights, 1994 Dec 31; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - The Links Series, 1995 May 02; 3 Cassettes Two DAT Tapes labeled as "original master," DAT tape 1: Links 1-9, DAT Tape 2: Links 10 & 11. One Audiocassette labelled "The Links Series/ By Stuart Saunders Smith, Performed at the University of Akron, Side A: Links 8-11" [unclear is there is a Side B]. It is not been confirmed, but based on the dates and markings, it appears the DAT tapes are the master copies of the University of Akron performance, and the audio cassette is a dub copy of Links 8-11. (Box Shared Cassette Box 1)
      File contains recordings of The Links Series (includes Links 1-11) performed by the University of Akron on May 2, 1995.
    - Stuart Saunders Smith Retrospective, 1995 Oct 6-7; 3 Cassettes VHS T-120, Tapes 1 and 2, Tape 2 has a duplicate. Duplicates are labeled as Nov 6-7. (Box Shared Videotape 1)
      Stuart Saunders Smith Retrospective Tapes 1-2. October 6-7, 1995.
    - Each Moment an Ending, Percussive Rotterdam, 1996 Mar; 1 Cassettes UMatic tape (Box Shared UMatic 1)
    - Mux Trio, 1996; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Weeds in Ophelia's Hair; New Music for Recorder Vol. 3; Julia Whybrow, 1997; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Here and There; Stuart Saunders Smith; performances by NOVA, 1997 Jun - 1998 Mar; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Wind in the Channel; Stuart Saunders Smith, 1997; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - When Music is Missing Music Sings, 1998 Sep 25; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Blue Too, performed by Peter Pollack, 1999 Mar 23 - May 12; 1 Cassettes Audiocassette (Box Shared Cassette Box 1)
    - Nicholas Hennies, Smith Memorial Hall, 1999 Apr 18; 1 Cassettes Audiocassette (Box Shared Cassette Box 1)
    - Emmanuel Sejorune; Withered Leaves-New Birth; Music for Mallets by Almada, Battistelli, Kerger, Mache, Manoury, Smith, Takemitsu, 2000; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - SO Percussion Group; Music for Percussion Quartet, 2000-2001; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - SO Percussion Group Demo CD, 2000-2001; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Crossfade; The Hoffman/Goldstein Duo, 2001; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Nicholas Hennies, Audition Tape, circa 2001; 1 Cassettes Audiocassette (Box Shared Cassette Box 1)
    - Verederos; In Common, 2002; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Smith-Bones (premiere); Helix! NME Rutgers University, 2002 Mar 03; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Bones, 2002 Mar 03; 1 Cassettes Audiocassette (Box Shared Cassette Box 1)
    - Music/Theater: New Dimensions, 2003; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Penelope Walcott; Songs to go to the Soul of Things, 2003; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Double Image; Compositions by Stuart Saunders Smith, 2003-2004; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Percussionist Songs; Arnold Marinissen, 2004; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Selections; Trio Spectra, 2004; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Here and There, 2004 May 05; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Endless; USW, circa 2004 Sep; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Breath: The Percussion Music of Stuart Saunders Smith, 2005; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - The Noble Snare; Compositions for Unaccompanied Snare Drum; performed by Jason Baker, 2005; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - 30 Jahre Musikwerkstatt in de Alten Schmiede, 2006; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Plenty; Berndt Thurner, vibraphone, 2006 Apr 23; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Plenty, circa 2006 May; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Duo Ego, 2006 Sep 29; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Sylvia Smith Percussion Duo; Iowa State University, 2006 Oct 04; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Plenty Premiere; Berndt Thurner, vibraphone, 2006 Oct 28; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - CMS New Music Concert; Rose Studio; Smith: "...and points north" for solo percussionist, 2006 Nov 02; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Music of Our Time; Sylvia Smith, percussion; Ayano Kataoka, percussion, 2007 Mar 07; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Family Portraits: Erika; Justin Dethaut (?), vibraphone; Nathan Schmidt, violin, 2007 Apr 29 - May 13; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - New Haven Quartet, 2007 May 03; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Roulette: Dept. of Hearts, 2007 Oct 26-30; 1 Compact Discs CD dated Oct 26 and two DVDs (one DVD Video dated Oct 26, one data DVD with eight tracks of audio dated Oct 30) (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
      File contains both audio and video for Roulette: Dept. of Hearts.
    - New College Florida, 2007 Nov 16; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Transitions and Leaps; New College Florida, 2007 Nov 16; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Sylvia Smith Percussion Duo, 2007 Mar 13; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - At Sixty Selections; Stuart Saunders Smith, 2008; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Books of Flutes; Carrie Rose, 2008; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - A Night at the "Opera"; music by Stuart Saunders Smith, 2008 Jan 31; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - UA Percussion Ensembles, 2008 Mar 07; 3 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Mike Lunde Recital, 2008 Apr 26; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Multiple Personality; Ta-Ting Wang, 2008 Apr 27; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Magdalene, 2008 May 17; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Interview with Stuart Saunders Smith by Rob Zuzin, circa 2008 Jun; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Sylvia Smith Percussion Duo, 2008 Sep 22; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - The Links Series of Vibraphone Essays; Stuart Saunders Smith, 2009; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Airborne, 2009; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - The New Cello, Vol. 1: American Composers; Works by Elliot Carter, Ben Johnston, Stuart S. Smith, and Franklin Cox; Franklin Cox, cello, 2009; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Tunnels; Lee Hinkle; Live Recital at UMBC, 2009; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - The Year Begins To Be Ripe; Percussion and Voices; Sylvia Smith performs music by Stuart Saunders Smith, John Cage, and Robert Erickson, 2009 Jan 27; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Four Seasons Concerts at Herbst Theatre; Thomas Buckner Recital with Joseph Kubera, piano; Beats by Stuart Saunders Smith, 2009 Mar 03; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Lee Hinkle, percussion; Doctor of Musical Arts Thesis Recital: Theatrical Pieces for Solo Percussion, 2009 Apr 08; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Strays, circa 2009 May; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Ian Kerr Master's Recital #1, 2009 Jun 07; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Hawk and Notebook Recording Sessions, 2009 Jun 8-9; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Ground; Session 5-19-2009, 2009 Jun 12; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Jennifer Ya-Ting Wang The Journey, 2009 Aug 16; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - Smith: Seven Seasons; Duo Ego, 2009 Sep; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 1)
    - The Isle Is Full Of Noises; Lisa Cella, flute, 2010; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Music for Keyboard Percussions; McCormick Percussion Group, 2010; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Vietnam Memorial; All material, rough mix/master, 2010 Feb 15; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Angels, 2010 Apr 01; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Percussion Music of Stuart Saunders Smith, 2010 Apr 10; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Percussion Sampler, 2010 Apr 26; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Breath performed at CCM, 2010 Jun 02; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Liglet for 2-part voices, 2011; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Rose; Rachel Bartz and Salvatore Sciarrino, flute, 2011 Jun 01; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Pinetop; Kyle Blair, 2011 Sep 22; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Jacob Dike Links No. 6 Rehearsal, 2011 Oct 30; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Pinetop; Kyle Blair, 2011 Nov 04; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Smith: Breath; Duo Ego Element Studies, 2011 Dec; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Pinetop, 2011 Dec 07; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - SSS: A River, Rose, 2011 Dec 09; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Edges; Duo Links, 2012; 1 Compact Discs DVD; 1 Folders Liner notes (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2, Box Correspondence 6, Folder 3)
    - Concerti for Strings with Percussion Orchestra; McCormick Percussion Group, 2012; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Tuning 1-2, 2012 Feb 12; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Shadows, Fires, and Cadences; UCSD Advanced Improv Ensemble, 2012 Feb 16; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Pinetop, 2012 Mar 05; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Notebook 10-09-2012 rehearsal, 2012 Oct 09; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - The Authors; Lee Hinkle, 2013; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Nocturne; Brett William Dietz, 2013; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - When Still: New Music for Solo Vibraphone; Zeca Lacerda, 2013; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Bones; Springs Theatre, 2013 Feb 07; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Music for Unspecified Instruments; McCormick Percussion, 2013 May 14; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Penka Kouneva Chamber Music; A Liturgy of the Hours run-through, 2013 May 29; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Noise Bridge; Live in Esslingen, 2013 Jun 28; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - On: Empty; Rehearsal, 2013 Sep 04; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - My Friend Gite Said and On: Empty World Premiere; Joseph Van Hassel; Capital University, 2013 Sep 17; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Bamfl Centre Recital; Zeca Lacerda, 2013 Oct 08; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Winter; 1st Master, 2013 Oct 12; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Palm Sunday, 2013 Oct 29; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Jude Traxler and Joseph Van Hassel, 2013 Nov 12; 2 Compact Discs One CD and one DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
      File includes both an audio CD and video on DVD.
    - Origins Concert Series, 2013 Nov 16; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Thicket; Anne Rainwater, piano, 2013 Nov 24; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Book of Horizons; Music by Michael Byron, Julius Eastman, Stuart Saunders Smith, "Blue" Gene Tyranny; Joseph Kubera, piano, 2014; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - A River Rose: Music for Violin; Stuart Saunders Smith; Airi Yoshioka, violin, 2014; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Correlates; solo percussion commissions; Joseph Van Hassel, 2014; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Fences; in Three Tragedies, 2014 Jan 07; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Stuart Saunders Smith Portrait Concert UCSD, 2014 Jan 30; 3 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Joseph Van Hassel; Ohio University, 2014 Feb 18; 2 Compact Discs One CD and one DVD (labeled "Joseph Van Hassel; Ohio University Recital") (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
      File contains both audio and video recordings Joseph Van Hassel's recital at Ohio University.
    - Joseph Van Hassel; Center for New Music, 2014 Mar 04; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Joseph Van Hassel; CNMAT, 2014 Mar 06; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - USF Percussion Concert, 2014 Nov; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Smith Productions Percussion Sampler, 2014 Dec 21; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Crux; Stuart Saunders Smith, 2015; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Hawk: The Saxophone Music of Stuart Saunders Smith, 2015; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Plot: Music for Unspecified Instrumentation, 2015; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - PASIC 2015; Bill Sallack and Stuart Saunders Smith, 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Sean Hamilton, 2015-2017; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Origins Concert Series; Composer Portrait: Stuart Saunders Smith, 2015 Feb 28; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Graduate Percussion Trio, 2015 Mar 28; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Alex Casimo DMA 2 Recital, 2015 Apr 26; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Full Circle; NOISE; CD-Text Replication Master; Test #1, 2015 Nov 27; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - New England; Version 2016, circa 2016; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Retrospective; "Unfinished Masters", 2016; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Queen Anne's Lace, 2016 Jan 04; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - The Hartt Graduate Percussion Group, 2016 Feb 19; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Lazarus; Joseph Van Hassel, xylophone; Poems; UNC Pembroke, 2016 Mar 23; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Untitled, circa 2016 May; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Stuart Saunders Smith and Joseph Van Hassel; UNC Pembroke, 2016 Mar 23; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Lazarus; Mix as of June 2016, 2016 Jun; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Smith: The Circle of Light; Krisztina Der, 2016 Aug 31; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Krisztina Der; flute/light recital; Browne Theater; UNC Pembroke, 2016 Sep 17; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - And Then There Was Light, 2016 Dec 03 - 2017 Jan 22; 1 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Pluralities, 2017; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - And Then There Was Light, 2017 (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
      [This recording was moved from the dissertation "And Then There Was Light: Lighting Art in Flute Repertoire."]
    - Quilt and Wellspring; Joseph Van Hassel and Jude Trexler, 2017; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Links No. 6 and Song Intersions (?), circa 2017 Jan; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - LOCI Live on WKCR-FM, 2017 Jan 23; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Recent Music of Stuart Saunders Smith, 2017 Mar 30; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Commune 1-4; UCSD, 2017 Apr 28; 2 Compact Discs Disc 1: Commune 1 & 2, Disc 2: Commune 3 & 4 (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Retro, 2017 May 16; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Heaven and Earth, circa 2017 Jun; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - A Liturgy of the Hours; Sylvie La Croix, 2017 Sep 13; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Smith Celebration Concerts, 2017 Nov 03; 2 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Origins Concert Series, 2017 Nov 04; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Bob USF, 2017 Nov 05; 2 Compact Discs DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Honesty VA; Sylvia La Croix and Berndt Thurner, 2017 Nov 08; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - A Liturgy of the Hours; Sylvia La Croix, 2017 Nov 08; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - New England; Stuart Saunders Smith; Berndt Thurner, 2018; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Shine; Lisa Cella, flutes; Stephen Bradley, video, 2018; 2 Compact Discs CD/DVD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - When Two Halves Come Full Circle; Sean Hamilton, 2018; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - The Lillies of the Field; Recording Session, 2018 Jan; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Angels v.3, 2018 Feb 11; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Mercy; McCormick Percussion Group, 2018 Feb 27; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Kyle Adam Blair Dissertation Recital, 2018 Apr 06; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - A Vietnam Memorial; Edited Test Master, 2018 Apr 23; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - University at Buffalo, 2018 May 06; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - Geography of Streams; Douglas Perkins, circa 2018 Jun; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2)
    - At Seventy, 2018 Sep 05; 5 Compact Discs CD; 1 Folders Liner notes (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 2, Box Correspondence 6, Folder 4)
    - 1-4, undated; 4 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 3)
    - 1. Otte: Correlater; 2. Smith: My Friend Gita Salad; 3. Macbride: March Madness; 4. Van Hassel: Here Connor, undated; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 3)
    - Angels; Appalachian State University Percussion Trio, undated; 1 Compact Discs CD; Data CD containing a .zip file with AIFF and WAV files at various bit rates and sample rates. (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 3)
    - Angels, undated; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 3)
    - Angels and Such Falling, undated; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 3)
    - Angels Edit 2, undated; 1 Compact Discs CD (Box Recordings-CD/DVD Box 3)